<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Features on RocketGate®</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Features on RocketGate®</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Processing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/advanced-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/advanced-processing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;advanced-processing&#34;&gt;Advanced Processing&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Choose RocketGate’s responsive technology to avoid loss from datacenter outages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many processors use a single datacenter with a “disaster recovery” model for so-called high availability.  In this model, if one datacenter fails, then technicians are alerted who then try to address the problems with this datacenter.  If they are unable to do so expediently, they begin the process of bringing their “disaster recovery” datacenter online. Outages, even partial outages, are obviously very costly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Reporting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/advanced-reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/advanced-reporting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;advanced-reporting&#34;&gt;Advanced Reporting&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;RocketGate&amp;rsquo;s advanced reporting system, “Mission Control” gives you the information necessary to make well-informed business decisions. Real-time reports are available online so you can view data anytime, anywhere. Mission Control allows you to view reports in a variety of formats such as HTML, CSV, PDF and XML. Merchants wishing to integrate data into in-house reporting applications can utilize an API to retrieve any of the reports programmatically.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mission-control-answers-key-business-questions-like&#34;&gt;Mission Control answers key business questions like:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How many members do I have and what is my recurring success rate?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which of my merchant accounts performs the best?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Do I have a bad affiliate?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What is my pricing “sweet spot”?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What are the best days of the week for sales &amp;amp; marketing initiatives?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How can I configure my load balancing to take advantage of the bank with the best authorization rates?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Detailed dashboards, reports and graphs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Printer-friendly PDF and graphical views of data&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Export to CSV/Excel&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-small-sampling-of-reports-in-mission-control&#34;&gt;A small sampling of reports in Mission Control:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Real time sales with daily $ and transaction total projections&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sales by hour comparing today’s sales with prior sales for that day of the week (ex: Monday’s sales versus past 8 Mondays)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Batch report&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Decline report with the ability to track decline reasons over time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chargeback with cross referencing of many different factors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Membership/Recurring&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Approval Ratio&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hosted Page traffic to sales conversion&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/missioncontrol2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Chargeback Processing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/automated-chargeback-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/automated-chargeback-processing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;automated-chargeback-processing&#34;&gt;Automated Chargeback Processing&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Protect your business with RocketGate’s automated chargeback processing service. When a chargeback, retrieval or reversal is received (via a daily digital feed),RocketGate will automatically mark the transaction as a chargeback, cancel a subscription (if applicable), block the customer from making future purchases, add the credit card number to a negative database and then send the data to the merchant via postback.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tool suite also includes a Chargeback Queue tool that lists retrieval and chargeback data for review with built-in workflow management. In addition, RocketGate’s sophisticated reporting helps to identify fraudulent activity from affiliates, consumers and issuing banks &lt;strong&gt;before&lt;/strong&gt; chargebacks occur. This proactive approach improves your bottom line. Retrieval requests and chargebacks can be responded to efficiently and easily in order to get reversals as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merchant Support Tools</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/merchant-support-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/merchant-support-tools/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;merchant-support-tools&#34;&gt;Merchant Support Tools&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Manage customer accounts with RocketGate’s full suite of merchant support tools including tools for transaction lookups, subscription/recurring membership information updates and refunds, both full and partial. You have the ability to respond to retrieval requests and chargebacks quickly and easily.  RocketGate’s Customer Support Tool Suite features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Real time Transaction and Membership Management dashboards&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Customer and transaction lookup tools - locate customers and/or transactions efficiently using one or multiple search parameters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Refund tool - issue a single credit or a batch of refunds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Full and partial refunds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;PCI compliant manual and scheduled re-bill transaction processing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Virtual Point of Sale tool - process phone or fax orders easily&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Membership management - cancel memberships and modify renewal and cancel dates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chargeback Queue Tool - list retrieval and chargeback data for review with built-in workflow management&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Risk Management tools - search for, monitor and/or block risky transactions or customers based on your own and/or Rocketgate’s Fraud Prevention Policies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;customer-retention&#34;&gt;Customer Retention&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For merchants with subscription-based business models, customer retention is a key indicator of performance. Even a seemingly small increase in customer retention will significantly improve the bottom line over the long run.  RocketGate provides many sophisticated tools that help merchants make well-informed business decisions regarding customer retention.  In addition, RocketGate’s sophisticated fault-tolerant gateway helps maximize customer retention.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;multiple-currencies&#34;&gt;Multiple Currencies&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;RocketGate’s high-performance gateway supports more than 60 different currencies, so you can efficiently expand your business by selling to international customers . International customers can view and pay with their own currency – which reduces credit requests and chargebacks. You have the added convenience of settlement and reporting in your local currency. RocketGate supports multiple US-based and offshore banks.  Features include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;table class=&#34;data_table&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;th&gt;Multi-Currency Solution&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;th&gt;Real Time Currency Conversion&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Offshore bank support in multiple regions of the world including Europe, Latin American and the Caribbean&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td class=&#34;dark&#34;&gt;Save $ and time with real time currency conversion – Example: Run a transaction in EUR but have it settle in US$&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td class=&#34;dark&#34;&gt;Support for all widely used currencies&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Support for all widely used currencies&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;Example:&amp;nbsp; EUR -&amp;gt; USD&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td class=&#34;dark&#34;&gt;No wire fees from foreign banks&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td class=&#34;dark&#34;&gt;Example:&amp;nbsp; GBP -&amp;gt; USD&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;td&gt;No foreign corporation setup required&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of the currencies we currently process.  Please note that we can easily add new currencies by request:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCI Compliant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/pci-compliant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/pci-compliant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;pci-compliant&#34;&gt;PCI Compliant&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;RocketGate is a Tier 1 certified Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliant service provider.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;float: right;&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/pci-badge.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;ayment &lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt;ard &lt;strong&gt;I&lt;/strong&gt;ndustry &lt;strong&gt;D&lt;/strong&gt;ata &lt;strong&gt;S&lt;/strong&gt;ecurity &lt;strong&gt;S&lt;/strong&gt;tandard (PCI DSS) is a set of requirements designed to ensure that &lt;strong&gt;all&lt;/strong&gt; companies that &lt;strong&gt;process&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;store&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;transmit&lt;/strong&gt; credit card information maintain a secure environment. The PCI DSS is administered and managed by the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/&#34;&gt;PCI SSC&lt;/a&gt;, an independent body that was created by the major payment card brands (Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover and JCB.).  It is important to note, the payment brands and acquirers are responsible for enforcing compliance, not the PCI Security Standards Council.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurring Billing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/recurring-billing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/recurring-billing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;recurring-billing&#34;&gt;Recurring Billing&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maximize profits with RocketGate’s easy to use, flexible and highly configurable recurring/subscription billing options and watch your revenue stream steadily grow. Features include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advanced flexible and easy-to-use APIs for complex recurring and subscription products including:&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Simple recurs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Paid trials&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Free trials&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Choose a recurring billing schedule based on days, weeks, months, quarters, year, and lifetime&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Instant upgrades&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Prorated upgrades&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Authorization-only including $0 auths&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cancel promos&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Recurring billing rate and/or frequency modification (gold upgraded to silver or monthly changed to quarterly)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Step down rebills&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Rebills run continuously throughout the day so that a 1 day trial always gets a full 24 hours of access.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Configure frequency of renew batches to maximize profits&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Configurable transaction retry schedule&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With RocketGate’s advanced membership reporting tools, you can:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/risk-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/risk-management/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;risk-management&#34;&gt;Risk Management&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;RocketGate&amp;rsquo;s sophisticated risk prevention algorithms precisely and effectively lower your chargeback ratios while increasing your revenues. Put RocketGate&amp;rsquo;s multi-level, intelligent, proprietary risk prevention software to work for your business. Risk reporting recognizes fraud patterns with built-in affiliate, customer and transaction risk tools and reports, identifying leading indicators of fraud before fraudulent transactions turn into chargebacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/profitability.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rocketgate’s tools can also be used to identify real-time risks, cross-reference multiple data-rich blacklists, deny re-entry and proactively refund high-risk transactions in an effort to eradicate chargebacks. Start using RocketGate’s tools and intelligent technology today to improve your bottom line tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
