<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Payment-Processing-Services on RocketGate®</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Payment-Processing-Services on RocketGate®</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Affiliate Tracking</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/affiliate-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/affiliate-tracking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;affiliate-tracking&#34;&gt;Affiliate Tracking&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RocketGate supports the following Affiliate Admin and Analytics Programs:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#39;display: grid; grid-template-columns: 50% 50%;&#39;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.toomuchmedia.com/pp_nats.htm&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;float: left;&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/aff_nats.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Running an affiliate program in today&amp;rsquo;s market requires a stable, scalable platform which is highly configurable and allows you to run your program how you see fit. NATS lets you analyze and maintain affiliate relationships, deliver and track advertising tools, configure unlimited offers, and generate detailed reports. Integrated with many of today&amp;rsquo;s billing options.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gateway</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/gateway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/gateway/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;gateway&#34;&gt;Gateway&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;RocketGate’s sophisticated and easy to use APIs (application programming interface) in multiple languages (PHP, Java, Ruby, Python, .NET etc) enable sample code-to-processing in minutes. &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/files/gateway-init.png&#34;&gt;See the Lifecycle of a Gateway Transactions.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;features-include&#34;&gt;Features include:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support for all major credit cards including Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover, JCB, ChinaUnionPay, BC Card, Diners Club, Maestro and Solo.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multiple currency support (see Multiple Currency page for complete list of supported currencies)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support for merchants based in the United States and across the globe&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tokenized processing (link to anchor tokenized processing for details)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Simple per transaction pricing (no %-based fees)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Configurable for multiple merchant accounts in order to support business continuity for acquirer and processor failures –&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;including load balancing and cascading across multiple banks, merchant accounts and processor&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;load balancing by card issuer, currency, volume and website&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-few-examples-of-load-balancing-routing-and-cascading-scenarios&#34;&gt;A few examples of load balancing, routing and cascading scenarios:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;load balance and cascade across 2 accounts - 50% to account #1 and 50% to account #2&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;100% to a single account with a cascade to a 2nd account&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;route to 3 accounts:  Maestro/Solo to account #1, Visa/Mastercard to account #2, JCB to account #3, EURO to account #3&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Site based load balancing for merchants with multiple websites&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;tokenized-payment-processing&#34;&gt;Tokenized Payment Processing&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This can be used whether you are connected to RocketGate via Gateway or Hosted Page or Hosted Form methods. RocketGate returns a unique token after the initial transaction that allows you to process subsequent transactions, such as recurring billing or repeat purchases, without storing credit card data. This feature is supported by both our Gateway and Hosted Page solutions. See the lifecycle of &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/files/gateway-token.png&#34;&gt;Gateway Tokenized Transactions&lt;/a&gt; and the lifecycle of &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/files/hosted-page-token.png&#34;&gt;Hosted Page Tokenized Transactions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosted Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/hosted-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/hosted-form/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hosted-form&#34;&gt;Hosted Form&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hosted Form is engineered for those who want maximum branding control and flexibility.  In the Hosted Form solution, you host the purchase page and include an iFrame from RocketGate where the credit card data is entered by the customer and then is transmitted directly to RocketGate.  This gives customers a seamless purchase experience from beginning to end.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/interactive-diagram/index.php&#34;&gt;Compare the Hosted Page vs Hosted Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/files/hosted-form.png&#34;&gt;See the lifecycle of a Hosted Form Transaction.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosted Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/hosted-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/hosted-page/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hosted-page&#34;&gt;Hosted Page&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Engineered for merchants who want the easiest integration or who do not want to host an SSL (secure sockets layer) site. In the Hosted Page solution, you link to a purchase page (hosted by RocketGate) where RocketGate securely collects credit card data on your behalf so you don’t have to store, transmit or process the credit card data. You control the look and feel of this page via the use of CSS (Cascading Style Sheets).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prevent Chargebacks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/prevent-chargebacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/prevent-chargebacks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;prevent-chargebacks&#34;&gt;Prevent Chargebacks&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RocketGate offers the following automated Chargeback Prevention systems:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#39;display: grid; grid-template-columns: 40% 60%;&#39;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.verifi.com/solutions-sellers/prevent-disputes/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;float: left;&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/verifi-cdrn-auth-reseller-logo.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While chargebacks are costly and painful, they can be prevented. Verifi&amp;rsquo;s innovative Cardholder Dispute Resolution Network™ (CDRN) is a patented and award-winning Saas based chargeback management program that prevents chargebacks and protects your payments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ethoca.com/eliminate-chargebacks&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;float: left;&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/ethoca-logo.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ethoca is a secure network for card issuers and merchants to connect and work cooperatively outside the payment network in a unique and powerful way!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;Ethoca, through its innovative services, helps connect card issuers to online merchants to stop fraud that slips through their defences and recapture lost revenues.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopping Carts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/shopping-carts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/shopping-carts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;shopping-carts&#34;&gt;Shopping Carts&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RocketGate currently supports the following shopping carts:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#39;display: grid; grid-template-columns: 50% 50%;&#39;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;float: left;&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/sc_prestashop.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PrestaShop comes complete with over 310 features that have been carefully developed to assist business owners in increasing sales with virtually little effort. All features are integrated in the software and are 100% free.  Learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;https://prestashop.com/&#34;&gt;PrestaShop&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;float: left;&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/sc_magento.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Magento’s founding officers built this Open Source e-commerce solution to give merchants full control over the look, content and functionality of websites. Because this product has full scalability and uses some of the newest technology, it can grow with the specific needs of today’s sophisticated merchants and accommodate seasoned merchants who want to keep up with the ever-changing market. Learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;https://business.adobe.com/products/magento/magento-commerce.html&#34;&gt;Magento&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPOS (Virtual Point-of-Sale)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/vpos-virtual-point-of-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payment-processing-services/vpos-virtual-point-of-sale/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;vpos-virtual-point-of-sale&#34;&gt;VPOS (Virtual Point-of-Sale)&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Virtual Point of Sale (VPOS) system is an easy online option for processing credit card transactions for orders that come via phone or fax.  You can connect to the VPOS in Mission Control via any online computer.  RocketGate’s web-based electronic transaction management system utilizes RocketGate’s high-speed gateway as well as its proprietary fraud prevention system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;rocketgates-vpos-system-features&#34;&gt;RocketGate’s VPOS system features:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Issue authorizations and capture funds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Issue refunds, both full and partial&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Void transactions prior to batch closure&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Seamlessly integrated with fraud prevention system with ability for merchant to turn scrubbing off for a particular transaction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Rebill prior transactions in a PCI compliant manner&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Setup recurring transactions including term limited (example: 12 payments of $x)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bill in multiple currencies with real time currency conversion&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/vpos.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
